etmedialabs.com 2014-12-19

# Online Advertising & Digital Media Marketing Company | ET Medialabs | India's Best Internet Agency

## Introduction:

ET Medialabs has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to theprivacy of visitors to our site. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for etmedialabs.com, and any other website through which we conduct business. After reviewing the Privacy Policy, if you have any further questions, please contact us at privacy@etmedialabs.com.

### A general note on internet technologies and privacy:

Before you review this Privacy Policy, we recommend you are familiar with the following concepts and terms so that you can best understand how ET Medialabs and its Clients use data about you and other Internet users to display better, more interesting advertising to you as you browse the Internet:

**Ad Tags:** Ad Tags are pieces of code that allow the delivery of online advertisements in the dedicated ad spaces on websites and in online applications. ET Medialabs Ad Tags may transmit certain anonymous information about the web site, section of the site and size of the ad that we are optimizing.

**API:** An application programming interface or “API” is a particular set of rules and specifications that allows one software program to access and make use of another software program. It helps facilitate the interaction between applications, similar to the way the user interface facilitates interaction between humans and computers. ET Medialabs uses API to make a bid request on RTB inventory sold by Supply Partners.

**Cookies:** Cookies are small text files that web servers typically send to users’ computer when they visit a website. Cookies can be read or edited when the user loads a website or advertisement from the domain that wrote the cookie in the first place. Cookies are used by companies to collect and send information about a user’s website visit – for example, number of visits, average time spent, pages viewed, navigation history through the website, and other statistics. This information can be used to improve a user’s online experience by saving passwords, or allowing companies to track and improve website loading times, for instance. Cookies can also be used to track a user’s browsing or online purchasing habits and to target advertisements to specific users. Cookies cannot be used to access any other data on a user’s hard drive, to personally identify them, or to act like malware or a virus. Users who prefer not to accept cookies can set their Internet browser to notify them when they receive a cookie or to prevent cookies from being placed on their hard drive

**Personally Identifiable Information:** We define personally identifiable information (or “PII”) as “information that can be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate a single person or can be used with other sources to uniquely identify a single individual.” e. g. name, address, phone number, e-mail address etc. This is the common industry definition used by most Internet companies. Information that is collected by various Internet companies but which does not qualify as PII is call “non-PII.”

**Real-Time Bidding:** Real-Time Bidding (or “RTB”) is a method of buying online or mobile advertising inventory by responding in real-time to an ad call with a “bid,” usually priced by cost per thousand impressions (“CPM”), to buy that single impression and thus the opportunity to display an ad to that user. RTB buyers use multiple different data sources, including third parties, to more precisely target the ads they display.

**Web Beacons & Pixels:** A web beacon consists of a small string of code that represents a graphic image request on a web page, a page in an online application, or in an email. A graphic image can be associated with the web beacon, but is not required. When an image is present, usually the image is designed to blend into the background of the web page, application, or email in which it appears. Often a beacon will be placed by an online data collecting company without an image, so it is invisible to the user, and in the smallest discrete space possible on the screen. This is a “pixel” and is essentially an invisible web beacon. Pixels and web beacons can be used for site traffic reporting, unique visitor counts, advertising auditing and reporting, personalization, and other uses. They do this typically by writing or editing cookies on each user’s computer. Therefore, like cookies, they cannot be used to key log, copy personal files from your computer, or replicate like a virus. Most pixels and web beacons, including those used by ET Medialabs, collect only anonymous data. However, some may be used to collect PII, particularly in the case of email that contains a web beacon. In such cases, the data collected through the web beacon may be linked to the recipient’s email address or other information identifying the recipient.

## ET Medialabs’ service & the data it collects:

### We Do Not Collect Personally Identifiable Information.

We do not collect PII via our Service, and expressly forbid our Clients from sending us PII and also take all precautions to avoid receiving PII from our Clients. If, despite these measures, we do receive PII from a Client or we inadvertently send PII we have received from a Client to a third-party we shall take all measures to remove the PII from our servers and records and to make certain the third parties have removed the PII from their records as well.

### We Collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information About You.

We collect Non-PII via our Service, including but not limited to your IP host address, the date, time, and time zone of the ad request, pages viewed, browser type, the referring URL, and your computer’s operating system.

### We Use Cookies And Web Beacons And So Do Our Clients.

We use cookies and web beacons for select purposes. We use them in order to track when we deliver an advertising impression so that we can correctly credit it to a Demand Partner and invoice that Demand Partner. We also drop a cookie for counting frequency of exposure to a particular ad to meet a Demand Partner’s campaign objective around frequency capping. As a buyer of RTB inventory available for sale on sell-side platforms and exchanges (Supply Partner), we do map anonymized user identification number (“UID”) against Supply Partner’s anonymized UID so as to gain handle to the underlying impression and be able to serve appropriate ad on that impression.

### ET Medialabs’ security & storage procedures for your data:

ET Medialabs is conscious of the importance of your data to you and conscientious about protecting that data from loss, theft, or misuse. All of the non-PII data collected by ET Medialabs is stored using the same security measures that we use to protect our own proprietary corporate data. Only authorized users are able to access the data we collect and store. While we cannot absolutely guarantee the security of the data we store, we do use all commercially reasonable measures to protect this information. We retain the Non-PII collected via our Service at a user level for certain period in order to ensure that our Service is functioning properly. We retain data at an aggregated level – so that no individual user, albeit anonymous, could be picked out from the data – indefinitely for purposes of reporting and system analytics. If you have any questions about our security practices, please send an email to us at privacy@etmedialabs.com.

### ET Medialabs’ information sharing:

Unless you otherwise permit ET Medialabs to share the Non-PII information it has collected about you, it will only share that information with the following third-parties and in the following circumstances: (i) to the appropriate authorities when we reasonably believe we are obligated to do so by law, or in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including but not limited to, fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person; (ii) to a court of law, arbitration panel, or similar body to enforce or protect our rights either under law or as granted by an agreement; (iii) to the company or entity that acquires all or substantially all of ET Medialabs’ assets, including if the acquisition occurs as the result of ET Medialabs' bankruptcy; or (iv) to third parties that help us provide the Service to Clients, that act as Supply Partners on our RTB service, or that enter into strategic partnerships with the company which allow us to expand the Service for our Clients.

### Children under 13 years of age:

ET Medialabs’ advertising products and the Service are not intended for persons under 13 years of age, and are not intentionally developed for or directed to children. We do not knowingly solicit or collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly market our products or services to children under the age of 13.

### Changes to ET Medialabs’ privacy policy:

We may revise this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes and/or updates to the Privacy Policy will be updated directly on this page. We encourage you to visit this page periodically to review our current Privacy Policy so that you will always know what information we gather and how we may use that information. In the event we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy we will advise our Clients of those changes in advance.

### Contacting us:

Should you have any questions in regards to this Privacy Policy or ET Medialabs’ privacy practices, please contact our representatives at the following email and they will be more than happy to clarify and assist you in any way possible: privacy@etmedialabs.com, or by mail at: 

**ET Medialabs Pvt. Ltd.,  
1st Floor, 167-A,   
Opposite Select City Walk,   
Malviya Nagar, New Delhi - 110017**
